Guide to the Stanford University, 125th Committee, Records SC1308
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford University, 125th Committee, Records
2015-2016
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
SC1308
5 Linear Feet
Scope and Contents
Collection includes marketing and outreach materials, ephemera, as well as research and planning records.
Biographical / Historical
As Stanford approached its 125th anniversary, a committee was organized to plan a year of celebration & festivities commemorating the anniversary. Nicole Sunahara, director of special initiatives in the Office of Public Affairs, led the effort. Celebratory efforts included several events held in 2016, and the website http://125.stanford.edu.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Administrative transfers, 2016-2017.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research use. Audio-visual materials are not available in original format, and must be reformatted to a digital use copy.
Stanford University -- History.
- Publications, Ephemera, and Memorabilia, Accession ARCH-2017-076
  - 125th Anniversary Trails Walk, 2016 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - 125th event postcards, 2016 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Celebrating Founders symposium, 2016 Feb 24 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Thinking Big About Learning, 2015 Oct 18 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - 125 Beaded Necklace, 2016 (Box 2)
  - Keepsake Chocolate Tin: Presidential Inauguration: Celebrating 125 Years, 2016 Oct 21 (Box 2)
  - Keepsake Chocolate Tin: Stanford | 125 - Stanford Dish Scene, 2016 (Box 2)
  - Large cloth banner, red with white lettering, "125" logo and "1891-2016", 48 x 78 inches (Box 3)
  - Large synthetic banners (2), Red with "125" in white, 2016; 36 x 72 inches (Box 4)
  - Large synthetic banners (2), verso: "Celebrating 125" with image of campus & bay / recto: "Years to get here" with image of Hoover Tower, 2016; 36 x 72 inches (Box 4)
- Additional Materials, Accession ARCH-2017-278
  - Souvenir candy tins (3) with Stanford|125 log and iconic campus scenes (Box 1)
  - Mounted photographs, 2016 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Photographs, 2016 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Photographs, 2016 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Cardinal Service Brochure, 2016 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Postcards, 2016 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Stanford Daily Quasquicentennial Issue, 2015 Sep 25 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Stanford Observed, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Stanford Centennial Chronology, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Annotated campus maps, 2016 (Box 2, Folder 9)